worldwideworkathome.com 2009-04-29

# Terms / Privacy Policy

| 

**Terms of Use / Privacy Policy**

Use of this site implies acknowledgment of the following terms and conditions. We reserve the right to modify or change these terms as necessary. 

No part of this website may be copied or reproduced in any form without prior written approval. 

Links to other Sites.  We display links to other websites. Displaying these links does not imply that such links are endorsed or recommended by us. Please research any site or opportunity you are considering joining.

All content on this site is provided on an "as is" basis without warranties of any kind. This site shall not be liable for any damages, including (but not limited to) loss of data or downtime, in connection with the use of this site.

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors is important to us. This privacy policy outlines what types of information we receive and collect when you visit worldwideworkathome.com and how it is used. We will never sell your information to any third parties.

_Log Files._  As with most websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information collected in these log files includes your IP address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider), the browser used when visiting our site, the time of your visit, and which pages you visited. This information is only used for statistical purposes. 

_Cookies and Web Beacons._ Cookies are used to store information such as your login details at our Forum. We also use third-party advertisements on this site. During the ad serving process these advertising companies may use technologies such as cookies and web beacons, which send them information including your IP address, ISP, and browser type. This data is generally used for geotargeting purposes or for showing certain ads that may be of interest to you. If you wish to disable or turn off cookies you can do so through your browser options settings. 

_Interest-Based Advertising._   Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this and other websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at 

. 

Please _contact_ us if you have any questions or are unsure about any of these terms.
